Inventory of the Resistencia Nicaragüense Ejército records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Public relations: communiques, 1990 (Box-folder 51: 17-18)
- Public relations: communiques, letters, 1990 (Box-folder 51: 19)
- Public relations: communiques, memoranda, 1990 (Box-folder 51: 20)
- Public relations: communiques, memoranda, letters, 1990 (Box-folder 51: 21)
- Miscellany: proclamation, biographical data, 1991 (Box-folder 51: 22)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: receipts, bills, miscellany, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 51: 23)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: check stubs, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 51: 24)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: receipts, bills, canceled checks, other financial records, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 51: 25)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation, asylum: bills, other financial records, application, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 52: 1)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: miscellaneous financial records, letters, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 52: 2)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation, Nicaraguan Business Council, Asociación Cívica Resistencia Nicaragüense: bills, letters, miscellany, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 52: 3)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation, Miscellany: miscellaneous financial records, miscellany, 1990 (Box-folder 52: 4)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: receipts, bills, miscellaneous financial records, 1990 (Box-folder 52: 5-10)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: certification of appointment, 1989 (Box-folder 52: 11)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation: letters, 1990 (Box-folder 52: 12-13)
- Nicaraguan Resistance Educational Foundation, Centro de Rehabilitación y Aprendizaje Francisco Morazán: resolution, letters, lists, 1990 (Box-folder 52: 14)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: news dispatches, magazine, blank forms, miscellany, 1983 (Box-folder 52: 15)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: clippings, magazine, statutes, blank forms, miscellany, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 52: 16)
- Printed matter: clippings, 1989 (Box-folder 53: 1-3)
- Printed matter: clippings, news dispatches, 1989 (Box-folder 53: 4)
- Printed matter: clippings, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 5-7)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: clippings, propaganda drawings, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 8)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: newspaper issues, blank forms, 1992 (Box-folder 53: 9)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: pamphlet, shooting targets, miscellany, undated (Box-folder 53: 10)
- Printed matter, Miscellany: clipping, blank forms, undated (Box-folder 53: 11)
- Journalists: reports, memoranda, intelligence reports, medical reports, miscellaneous reports (Sección de Personal, Sección de Inteligencia, Cuerpo Médico), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 53: 12)
- Journalists: reports (Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas), 1990 (Box-folder 53: 13)
- Press visits: authorization memoranda, letters (Fiscalía Militar, Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas, Honduran officials), 1989 (Box-folder 53: 14)
- Press visits: authorization memoranda, letters (Oficina de Divulgación y Prensa, Fiscalía Militar, Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas, Honduran officials), 1990 (Box-folder 54: 1)
- Radio 15 de Septiembre, electoral process, peace process violations, prisoners of Sandinistas: agreement, position papers, reports, press releases, clippings, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 54: 2)
- Radio 15 de Septiembre: broadcast scripts, 1990 (Box-folder 54: 3-4)
- Radio 15 de Septiembre: radio frequency list, undated (Box-folder 54: 5)
- Contacts in Honduras: letters and memoranda to Honduran officials (Sección de Personal), 1990 (Box-folder 54: 6)
- Contacts in United States, contacts in Japan, Bloque Opositor de Sur, Miscellany: letters to or from American and Japanese officials, position papers, pamphlet, press releases, miscellany, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 54: 7)
- Friends of U.S.A. (Japanese organization): letters, 1988 (Box-folder 54: 8)
- Contacts in United States, public relations, state of force, Miscellany: press releases, memoranda, speeches, messages, biographical data, guard duty rosters, miscellaneous personnel lists, reports, Sandinista identification documents and certificates of service, blank forms, miscellany, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 54: 9)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: regulations, psychological warfare manual, combat statistics, 1987 (Box-folder 54: 10)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: sabotage manual, instructional materials, 1988 (Box-folder 54: 11)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: memoranda on psychological warfare training, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 54: 12)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: psychological warfare instructional materials, maps, personnel memoranda, miscellany, 1990 (Box-folder 54: 13)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: receipts, 1990 (Box-folder 54: 14)
- Psychological warfare, peace process violations, combat: messages, reports, statistics, clippings (Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas), 1989 (Box-folder 54: 15)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: messages (including messages re political meetings), 1990 (Box-folder 54: 16-17)
- Sección de Operaciones Psicológicas: logbook of messages, 1990 (Box-folder 55: 1)
- Propaganda: broadside, undated (Box-folder 55: 2)
- Propaganda: drawings, undated (Box-folder 55: 3)
- Propaganda: slogan stencils, undated (Box-folder 55: 4)
- Miscellany: certifications of service, personnel lists, 1991 (Box-folder 55: 5)
- Miscellany: bulletin, religious literature, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 55: 6)
- Miscellany: birth certificate, blank forms, 1982 (Box-folder 55: 7)
- Miscellany: document receipts, 1987 (Box-folder 55: 8)
- Miscellany: oath, undated (Box-folder 55: 9)
- Miscellany: map, bulletin, miscellany, 1982 (Box-folder 55: 10)
- Miscellany: map, blank forms, undated (Box-folder 55: 11)
- Miscellany: guides to archives, 1987 (Box-folder 55: 12-13)
- Miscellany: guides to archives, memorandum, 1989 (Box-folder 55: 14)
- Miscellany: guide to archives, undated (Box-folder 55: 15)
- Miscellany: templates, undated (Box-folder 55: 16)
- Miscellany: blank forms, undated (Box-folder 55: 17-25)
- CLOSED (Boxes 56-127)